A handgun bullet travels at more than 700 miles per hour.
Hey, whoa. Absolutely not. No.
Look, if you don't wanna do it, you don't have to do it.
Okay. Good, I don't wanna do it.
Fine.
Goddamn! I'm alive.
Oh!
Oh, that's amazing!
I know, right. So...
Hmm.
Ready to go again?
Absolutely not.
Fine.
Don't just say "fine" and then shoot me in the chest.
'Cause it's not cool.
Like at all.
Okay. Jeez.
I always wondered why no one tried to be a superhero before me.
It turns out somebody had. Mindy Macready.
After her dad died,
his old partner on the force, Marcus, became her guardian.
-Is that a Pink Pony bag she's wearing?     -Nice backpack.
Thanks.
Steal it from a six year old?
Marcus dropped her off every day.
But as soon as he was gone, so was she.
No one at school found out
because she hacked into the server
and gave herself the award for perfect attendance.
Hit Girl and Big Daddy had been the real deal.
Mindy was gonna keep wearing the mask
as long as there were criminals to take down.
But no matter how many drug dealers she stopped,
she couldn't stop feeling alone.
Me? I'd given up being a superhero
because it was way too dangerous.
Only problem, I was dying of boredom.
Like most high school seniors,
I had no idea what I wanted to do with my life.
Hell, I didn't know what channel I wanted to watch.
It's just TV, Dave, not peace in the Middle East.
My best friends Todd and Marty
had no clue I was the first superhero to go public.
You guys watch Spider-Man last night?
Is it weird that Aunt May gets me kinda hard?
Not if you're a granny-slammer.
They may wear costumes, but it isn't Halloween.
They're real life superheroes,
and in the two years since the first ordinary citizens
donned capes and masks,
the movement has started to spread.
I became a superhero because of Kick-Ass.
Yeah, you just come home from work,
you grab your gear and you go out on patrol.
Help us make the streets safe.
I inspired all those people to get off their asses,
and now I was stuck on mine.
So that night after dinner,
I decided to get my old costume out.
-Sorry.     -Whoa! Can't you knock?
You know, buddy, it's perfectly normal for you to touch yourself...
Oh, Jesus, Dad. Get out!
If I was even thinking about a Kick-Ass sequel,
I had to get serious.
Hey. Hey, can we chat?
Please, Mindy?
Get in the cab. Meter's running.
I wanna team up like Batman and Robin.
Nobody wants to be Robin.
What's wrong with Robin?
Weren't you like Big Daddy's Robin?
Robin wishes he was me.
What I'm trying to say is we should be partners,
you and me, like the dynamic duo.
I'm in the NFL, Dave. You play pee-wee.
So? Train me.
I wanna walk the walk,
and you're the closest thing I know to a real superhero.
Aren't you tired of being on your own?
Don't you wanna know someone's there for you?
Someone who's got your back?
And you'll do anything I say?
Anything.
Hit me.
You're a 15-year-old girl.
What the hell?
Act like a bitch, get slapped like a bitch.
Oh, goddamn.
Mindy beat me like morning wood
every day for three weeks.
Come on. Guard up! Left, right, guard up!
Even with my damaged nerve endings,
it hurt like hell.
But, in a weird way, I kinda liked it.
It gave me a sense of purpose.
-What happened to your face?     -Nothing.
Like we were driving towards something.
Goddamn!
Oh! Oh, that's amazing!
All the other people putting on masks were just playing superhero.
We were training to really do it.
I couldn't tell my girlfriend Katie, or Marty and Todd.
But I didn't care. We were having too much fun.
Left, right, left!
Our own superhero team.
It was gonna be balls.
What the hell, Mom? Did you delete the news off the DVR?
Yes. Yes, I did, Christopher.
That was the one with Kick-Ass.
Oh, Christopher, you've gotta stop obsessing over this superhero.
He is not a superhero, Mom, he's a murderer.
He blew up Dad with a bazooka, for fuck's sake!
Your father died in a fire.
A fire? What is your problem?
You! You are my problem!
I am trying to raise you to be a normal boy!
That's why we moved to Long Island after your father's accident.
A bazooka is not an accident,
you delusional bitch!
This conversation is over.
Great. Then I'm leaving.
Come on, Javier, be cool.
Sorry, Chris, but your mom pays me not to be cool.
I hate you! You home-school me like I'm a prisoner!
You threw away my Red Mist costume.
God! I am not the problem! You are!
I wish you were dead!
Mommy?
Don't touch that.
Oh, I'm sorry. What is it?
It's a last resort. Like if all else fails and you're about to die.
Are you not scared to die?
Are you scared you're never gonna grow into your big boy pants?
I'm serious.
What if Spider-Man or Batman got killed one night? It could happen.
If you're scared of dying, one thing is certain,
you are going to die.
My daddy was never afraid of dying.
Look where that got him.
He knew he might have to make the ultimate sacrifice one day.
And that's why he made me promise
I'd never stop defending this city.
Cross my heart,
hope to die.
Your dad was insane. You know that, right?
You're wrong, Dave.
My daddy was the first real superhero,
not you or Red Mist. It was my daddy,
and it was an honor to serve by his side.
Hey, Min, how was school?
Super crazy.
Miss Mullins was out today, so we had Mr. Cooper teaching us biology,
such a grump.
Oh, really? That's weird because Principal Himoff called me yesterday.
You were supposed to get an award for perfect attendance,
but you didn't attend.
I followed you this morning. Saw you get into a cab with some boy,
and I lost you guys over the bridge.
So now you wanna tell me where you really were today?
I'm really sorry, Marcus. I didn't wanna make you mad.
Cut the waterworks, Min. You're 15, not five.
Okay.
Look, he asked me to cut class and go to the mall.
So, yeah, yeah, I did.
This has nothing to do with you being Hit Girl?
I'm not gonna find any ninja blades or throwing stars under your bed?
No. I just wanted him to like me. Okay?
Sweetie, no skipping school's not away to get boys to like you.
-I'm so stupid.     -Hey, hey.
You're one of the smartest little girls I know. Let's go get some pizza.
What, you mean I'm not grounded?
Well, just consider this awarning.
Hey, you sure you wanna give all your mom's things away?
What the hell am I supposed to do with all her stuff?
Damn, she had a nice pair of guns.
Dude, she's dead! Don't talk about her tits.
I was talking about these.
Oh, those. Those were my dad's.
Why don't you keep them?
Are you sure?
Yeah. I mean, they belong to you, right?
Come on, Chris. You're your own man now.
-Just be careful, all right?     -Yeah.
Whoa!
Definitely don't wanna keep those!
I'll take care of it.
You take the day off. Later.
Hey.
So, are you ready for your first field test?
What am I supposed to do with these?
Put them on and, uh, go fishing.
I'm the whitest pimp ever.
That's the idea. Take the next right.
Comes out on Flatbush.
You sure I should be doing this without my gear?
That's the point.
Kick-Ass isn't a costume. Kick-Ass is who you really are.
Dave Lizewski is the mask.
Well, my "mask" is about to get his teeth kicked in.
Hey, queer bait, where are you going with those bags, man?
Tell him you're on your way to fuck his mother with a 12-inch strap on.
I'm just taking a walk.
This really isn't what I do. I usually just call the cops.
Who are you talking to, man?
Uh, I'm just on a call. It was...
You know, service round here, it sucks, man.
Now give me the bags, faggot,
before I make you suck my fat cock, huh?
Come on.
Okay, Okay.
Can you believe I let Mindy beat the snot out of me for weeks
just so I could get my ass kicked again?
So much for a team.
You ready to die? You faggot!
You know, all that homophobic shit makes you sound super gay.
Come on, man. Come on.
If I ever catch you robbing again, shit-burger,
I'm gonna go Saudi Arabia on your ass and cut your hand off.
Promise me you're done with your life of crime.
I promise.
Pants on fire.
-What do you think?     -I think you almost got me killed!
No. What do you think of my line?
"Pants on fire." I wrote a whole bunch of 'em.
Run! I'll tell them you saved me. Go!
Female suspect fleeing Flatbush.
Under 5 feet. Masked. Armed with nunchucks and a sword.
-Hey, Min.     -Hey, Marcus. What's up?
I see you answered your phone.
That means you're not in school.
I was,
but I wasn't feeling so good, and so the nurse decided to send me home.
Poor thing. Well, I'm almost home.
I'll make soup and we can watch Jeopardy!
All righty. I'll see you soon, okay?
All right.
Shit!
You got my soup?
Let me take your temperature first.
Oh, you're really clammy.
I'll feel better after a nap-nap.
Close your eyes. I'm gonna get you that soup.
Is that blood?
Damn it, Mindy. I can't do this anymore.
Your father was like a brother to me.
He was a great cop and a hero.
But Big Daddy? That was not your father, okay?
That was someone who robbed you of your childhood.
And this?
Hit Girl? That's not who you are.
You are Mindy Macready and you're just starting high school.
I understand that you don't know who that person is yet,
but you will, you've just gotta try.
I don't want to.
You don't know what you want.
You can't. You're not an adult, not yet.
Yeah, well, I've done more in my 15 years than most adults have in their lifetime.
That note that your father gave you,
the one that you were supposed to open if anything ever happened.
What did it say?
That you would take care of me.
And that you were supposed to listen to me, right?
Well, listen up.
I want you in school. I want you to stop talking to that boy.
And I want you to promise me
that this is never gonna happen again.
Cross my heart,
hope to die.
Good.
Mindy!
What the hell?
First you almost get me killed, then you stand me up.
Dave, I'm sorry.
I mean, I... you are?
I am.
For everything.
Oh, okay, great.
I mean, "apologetic" isn't a word I'd use to describe you.
How many times do I have to say it?
Look, let's get out of here.
You gotta ease up. I think I might have broken a rib.
Dave, I'm done.
With training?
With everything.
Wait, you mean everything?
You can't. You're Hit Girl.
We were gonna start a team, you can't just quit.
This is who you are.
Not anymore, Dave.
I'm sorry, but it's over. I'm done.
She just broke up with him?
Just leave me alone.
Will you stop apologizing?
I don't know what's worse, that you're fucking a 9th-grader
-or that you just got dumped by one.     -Whoa, whoa!
Pedophile freak.
It's not like that.
Then what is it like? Please, tell me.
I can't. It's to do with the Kick-Ass thing.
I've got a secret for you. You remember Malik?
Dude who volunteers at your needle exchange?
His baton is so much bigger than Kick-Ass'.
-No.     -Yeah.
And by "baton," I mean penis.
Yeah, I got that. Thanks.
Fifteen gets you 20, pervert.
A freshman, Dave? You old, salty dog.
What's the problem? Grass on the field, play ball. Right?
No, Todd.
Chris, your tutor's here.
Chris!
Chris, your...
Holy shit. What the hell is that?
My destiny.
Chris, just because your mom liked to get a little freaky now.
I know what my role is in this, Javier.
My dad was a crime boss, so it just makes sense.
I'm a supervillain. It's evolution.
Come on, come on.
Just put those things down before you hurt somebody, Chris.
That's not my name.
Okay, okay. Uh, Red Mist...
Red Mist was my superhero name.
Henceforth I'll be known as
The Motherfucker.
After Mindy quit,
I decided to stop hitting the heavy bag and start hitting the streets.
Hey, Kick-Ass, welcome back!
-Yeah!     -Whoo!
You're the best, man!
Only problem, I was still on my own.
So I went online and found a physics professor
calling himself "Dr. Gravity."
Sure, he wasn't Hit Girl, but I had to start somewhere.
This is the zero G device that I invented.
Can levitate any object up to a ton.
For real?
Hell, no, man. This is a baseball bat wrapped in tinfoil.
But it fooled you.
Hey, could I get a Diet Mountain Dew, please?
I'm not even a physics professor.
Just a copywriter for an ad agency.
But that's why I love this stuff.
You can be anyone you want!
You done many team-ups before?
Kind of. Yeah. No, not really.
I was getting kinda nervous about being on my own, you know?
Yeah, me, too. I never even been in a fight.
Well, hopefully you won't have to.
I friended a guy talking about forming a team, if you're interested.
I don't know how serious he is,
but his picture was pretty hard core.
Are you kidding me? That's why I contacted you.
I didn't wanna freak you out by bringing it up too soon.
I'll show you his profile after I hit the men's room.
Your Uncle Ralph's not gonna be happy about this, Chris.
That's not my name.
I'm not calling you that, forget it.
Javier, you worked for my dad.
Then you worked for my mom. Now you work for me.
I'm probably the richest kid in New York City.
But if you don't like that, find yourself another motherfucking job, okay?
Yo, Kick-Ass!
Man, am I glad to see you.
Is there anything I can do to help, sir?
Yeah. I was hoping you can help me get a million hits on YouTube.
Come on. Come on.
Run, Kick-Ass, run!
Jersey Shore motherfucker!
Hey, what, you not interested in a fair fight?
That is no fair fight. Team meeting tomorrow.
I'll e-mail you the address.
Beware Dr. Gravity!
You had to admire the Doctor's enthusiasm.
I couldn't wait to meet his friends.
Hands in the air, Spring Roll.
Empty the register and don't do anything stupid.
Come on! Hey, where are your security cameras?
-We don't have them. Too expensive.     -Seriously?
What the fuck? How's this gonna go viral?
You want to be filmed?
Shut up and just get on the ground!
And you'd better tell people The Motherfucker was here.
What's wrong with you, boy?
Get on the floor, too, Gandalf,
or I will bust a cap in your ass.
You're gonna bust your own face when that gun kicks if you don't hold it properly.
Just get on the ground!
God, will you hurry up!
I told you.
Go! Go, go, go!
Start the car! Go, go!
It was amazing!
I feel so alive.
I know who I am. I know why I'm here.
I'm gonna fuck this world up!
They will know The Motherfucker's name!
You've gotta find me some bad-ass MMA types to train me, okay?
Like a Chuck Liddell or whoever.
Fuck, I don't care how much it costs.
I just wanna be able to kill Kick-Ass with my bare hands.
I gotta tweet about this.
All right. Are you ready?
Um, I don't know. Am I?
Yes, you are. You look great.
And Barbara's daughter, Brooke, is really nice.
What am I supposed to talk to them about?
I'd rather be water-boarded than listen to Justin Bieber.
-You're gonna be fine.     -I'm gonna be a disaster.
How do you know that?
Because it's a slumber party, for fuck's sake.
Dollar. Jar.
You're gonna need a bigger jar.
Pretty cool, huh? This is how the beer gets delivered.
Dude. You got a secret elevator to your underground headquarters.
Yeah. The guy I told you about owns this place.
It's like a real-life bat-cave.
-I know, right.     -Oh, yeah.
This is the single greatest thing I've ever seen.
Welcome to Justice Forever.
Hi, Detective Williams. This must be Mindy.
It is. Hi, Brooke.
You girls have fun and I'll pick you up in the morning, okay?
I'll be the one with the slit wrists.
No, you're gonna be the one that gets the awesome manicure.
-I am?     -Mmm-hmm. Oh, yeah.
Say "hey" to Mindy, ladies.
Hey.
I know you.
You're that freshman who took a ride on Dave Lizewski's disco stick.
I did not ride his...
If you just blew him, you're totes a virgin, right?
She didn't blow him, look at her.
Then what? Rim job? Hand job? Fingerbang?
Sweet-Ryan-Seacrest, you at least kissed him, right?
Totes.
You've never kissed a boy, have you?
Oh, my God, that is so adorable.
Maybe she's a dyke.
Maybe I'll jam my foot up your snatch.
Oh, she's super bitchy, I likes.
Then what's the big deal anyway?
What could be so great about gagging on some douche-bag's tongue?
It's pretty fucking great.
You know how you feel when you watch that video by Union J?
Holy shit, you don't know?
This will change your life.
♬ Don't ever say you're lonely Just lay your problems on me ♬
♬ and I'll be waiting there for you ♬
You guys love this shit more than fanboys love Stan Lee, don't you?
Who's Stan Lee?
♬ I'll carry you I'll carry you ♬
♬ I'll carry you ♬
♬ So you know that I'll carry you ♬
♬ Like you've been running for hours ♬
♬ And can't catch your breath ♬
♬ The demons are screaming so loud in your head ♬
♬ You're tired You're broken ♬
♬ You're cut and you're bruised ♬
♬ But nothing's too heavy Just hold on ♬
♬ I'll carry you ♬
What the fuck was that?
I know, right? I'm soaked.
That? That is who you are, Mindy.
You may not dress like us or talk like us,
but when it comes to boys, we're all the same.
Twilight. Channing Tatum. Union J.
It's biology, bitch. Don't fight it.
I, um...
I gotta go.
But we were gonna go and get high on bath salts at Logan's house.
Mindy, I wanna give you a chance that the rest of the girls in our class would kill for.
Don't you wanna walk out the door every day in skin-tight clothes
knowing that everyone worships you?
Don't you wanna sneak out at night, raise a little hell,
and show the world what a strong,
independent woman is capable of?
Don't you wanna belong?
♬ So you know that I'll carry you ♬
Can I wear this to Logan's?
Yay!
It's gonna be so much fun.
So we tried the cops and tried the newspapers,
and even set up a, you know, a thing on the Internet
for people to help us find Tommy.
Um...
But we got nothing. We never saw our son again.
I came up with the name Remembering Tommy,
and, uh, we've been doing this three nights a week. So...
Colonel Stars and Stripes found us online.
That's terrible, guys. I'm real sorry.
I became Night Bitch after my sister was murdered
and found in a dumpster.
Holy shit.
Doesn't bring her back,
but at least I'm doing something positive about it.
-Insect Man.     -Yeah, um...
I've been bullied my whole life for being gay,
so now I stand up for the defenseless.
That's why I don't wear a mask.
Too much like being back in the closet.
Long as your heart's in the right place,
we don't care what you put in your mouth.
-Fist bump.     -Thank you. Thank you, sir.
Well, I became Battle Guy,
after my parents were mugged and killed coming home from the opera.
Did I tell you that sick bastard,
maxed out their credit cards on porno sites?
I hope we get the chance to say hello to this guy someday,
so I can personally levitate his soul from his body.
Oh, my God. Marty?
Yeah, I knew I recognized your voice.
No, I don't know what you're talking about.
I don't know no Marty. New guy.
Hey, asshole, it's me, Dave.
Dave? Why are you dressed like Kick-Ass?
Because I'm Kick-Ass.
You two know each other?
Yeah, like since we were five.
What's all this bullshit about your parents getting killed?
-Yeesh, language.     -What?
Battle Guy, care to update your resume?
Uh...
I'm trying to figure out how to explain this,
without sounding like a complete idiot right now.
Yeah, I'm not sure that's possible, Batman.
I'm not, either.
Um...
Okay. Well, when I found you guys online,
you were all swapping these awesome origin stories.
I mean, Colonel, you're ex-Mafia, for Christ's sake.
Yo. Don't take the Lord's name in vain.
I'm sorry.
I didn't think you'd let me join the team,
unless I had a good story, too.
All right, we'll let you off the hook this time, Battle Guy.
-Wanna see something cool?     -Yeah.
I thought this could be our meeting room.
Whoa, this is so cool.
Now this little renovation was totally clandestine,
which means nobody knew about it.
Now, I know it's not much, but this is just the beginning.
Together we can make a real difference.
Whoa!
If you'd consider it, Kick-Ass,
we'd be honored to have you join us.
Hell, yeah!
That's what I like to hear.
Right, time for initiation.
Turn around and I'll unzip you.
I'm sorry, what?
Just joking. Let's get down to business.
Gotcha.
There you are.
We saved you a seat in the caf,
but you never showed.
I usually head over to the Olive Garden to carb load.
I haven't had white sugar since my first birthday.
Do we need a thintervention?
Come on, best way to tighten up a tummy is varsity dance team.
The sign-up sheet just went up.
It's still blowing my mind. Kick-Ass.
It's like finding out your best friend's,
always been Will Smith, you know?
Hi, guys. What are you talking about?
Nothing.
-Nothing?     -Yeah, Todd, nothing.
All right. See you around, guys.
Todd, wait.
-Ow, watch it.     -Watch me end your life.
Come on. Forget it.
Just one of the dickheads that follows The Motherfucker on Twitter.
Who?
The Motherfucker. He's some guy
claiming to be the world's first supervillain.
He's got 1,000 followers already.
What an asshole.
-Get some!     -Uh-huh! Yeah!
You got this, Motherfucker!
You really think he's got a shot?
I wouldn't take his money if I didn't.
MMA is like chess.
It's all about the moves.
And your boy really knows his stuff.
Time to die, asshole.
-You all right?     -I'm cool. Ow!
Good job. Nice jab, buddy.
Come on, stay loose, baby. Walk it off, walk it off.
-Oh!     -Shit!
Oh, you broke my leg!
-Come on. Do something.     -Let's take a break.
Yeah, yeah, let's take a break, guys. Come on.
Street rules, bitch!
Chuck! Get this girl off me!
Hey, what are you doing? What are you doing, man?
You all right, Chris? You all right, buddy?
Get off me! I was winning.
No, you were crying.
You know what? Screw this. My super power
is that I'm rich as shit.
Hey, you wanna work for me, huh?
You wanna beat people up for me?
-Sure.     -All right!
Let's get you a mask and a costume,
and we will call you Black Death.
Whoa, whoa, you don't think that's just a little bit incredibly racist?
I don't give a shit.
I want you to put the word out,
that I'm willing to pay top dollar, for every hired hitter in town.
Come on, come on. Just talk about it first.
Money talks.
You wanted me to be my own man.
This is what it looks like.
-All right, all right, I'll make some calls.     -Yes!
Anybody else wanna be a supervillain?
Promise I pay better than Chuck-little-dick-Liddell.
- What did you call me?  - No, no, man.
He took a hit to the head. Doesn't know what he's saying.
I've been studying privately with Coach Podell.
And by studying,
I mean my mom paid her off to make me varsity.
So, if you're half decent, I'll make sure she puts you on the team.
At least as an alternate.
You'd do that for me?
Besties stick together.
If Brooke wants a pet, she should just get a dog.
She's just trying to recreate Mindy in her own image.
All right, ladies, have a seat. Let's get started.
Mindy Macready?
Chill. As long as you don't fall on your face, you're in.
Go.
Four attackers.
No escape.
Oh, my God. You could totally make captain.
That was so much better than Brooke's.
Oh, my God.
Brooke doesn't stand a chance for captain after that.
A bunch of people with made-up names,
standing around in homemade costumes,
searching the web for unsolved crimes.
The comic book heroes all have billion-dollar bases
and headquarters on the moon, but this is the real world.
-Scales, like a red, white and blue.     -It's awesome.
- What's that?  - Brick.
Right.
-What do you think?     -I think it does the job.
People should get what they deserve.
Family living in the street deserves a hot meal.
An inebriated college girl deserves to make it home safe at night.
And a pervert, pedophile,
deserves a visit from Eisenhower.
Schwantz!
Ouch.
You don't wanna hit with your closed fist.
You might break your hand, then you're defenseless.
You wanna hit with open palm and pivot. Open palm and pivot.
Grab the back...
I never made varsity football,
or got cast in the school play.
Hell, I never even made honor roll.
Knock out, bitch!
But if I had,
I gotta believe it would've felt a lot like this.
When the cops can no longer protect and serve,
be warned, mugger, heads up, perv.
We got the strength, we got the nerve,
to give those in need what they deserve!
Justice Forever!
We were in the ultimate clique.
It didn't matter that no one else knew.
We knew. And we felt like rock stars.
-Good night, guys.     -Nice job. Battle Guy.
Night, Colonel. Thanks for everything.
No, son, thank you.
You showed us that every man can make a difference.
Without Kick-Ass, none of us would be here.
That's from the heart. Don't let it go to your head.
So...
I'm not really that tired.
Mmm.
Mmm-mmm?
Mmm. Okay.
Let's leave the masks on.
-Yeah?     -Yeah.
Yeah!
First big mission's tonight,
and it's not community service.
We're taking on some real bad guys.
What, can't your team handle it?
They're not you, Mindy.
Remembering Tommy owns a dry fruit business.
Night Bitch teaches ballet.
Night Bitch? What is she?
A superhero or a soft core porno?
Maybe a little bit of both.
Oh, God, you're plugging her?
I'm gonna vom.
You're like a ninja.
Can't you just sneak out after Marcus goes to sleep?
You don't get it, Dave.
I made a promise to Marcus.
So break it. You're a superhero, remember?
Mindy Macready's just a disguise.
Yeah, well, I don't know what kind of superhero Night Whore is,
but if you really think I'd ever break my word,
you obviously have no idea who I am.
I know that making dance team doesn't make you stop being who you are.
I know Hit Girl couldn't give a shit,
about what high school girls are into.
I know that you wouldn't go on a date if your life depended on it.
Go to hell, Dave.
What? You know I'm right.
Hey! Roid Rage.
-Me?     -Yeah.
You wanna take me on a date sometime?
Uh, yeah. Sure. Um...
My name's, um, Simon.
Great, um, Simon.
It's a date.
Mindy, I'm sorry.
Is there a problem, Min?
Zero.
Good. Because I don't like problems.
Dave, you been sneaking out at night?
Mrs. Neipert said, she thought she saw you leaving at 2:00 in the morning.
Miss Neipert's crazy, Dad.
She tried to teach her dog Spanish.
Are you on drugs?
Seriously?
I gotta ask.
You're my best bud and you're growing up so fast.
Promise me you're not doing anything foolish?
Yeah, I promise.
Good enough for me, pal.
You're too smart to do anything stupid.
Justice Forever!
I'm glad you got that out of your system.
Oh, Todd texted me. Again. What a loser.
Dude, how bad-ass is Colonel Stars and Stripes?
Yeah, I still can't believe he's an ex-mob enforcer.
I mean, how do you go from that to being a superhero?
He's a born-again Christian.
-Shut up.     -Yeah.
Let's hope he can handle tonight.
I guess we're about to find out.
Hey. Where's the rest of the team?
Dr. Gravity has the flu,
and Remembering Tommy got Book of Mormon tickets, so...
That's okay.
Five of us should do.
How did you say this guy made his money, sir? Prostitution?
Not just girls. Kids. Ships them in from villages back home.
Boneheads in blue take a blind eye.
How do you know he's here tonight?
Because Thursday night is poker night.
Same five low-lifes every week.
Man with a habit ain't hard to find.
So what's the plan? Are we sneaking in?
I thought we'd knock. It's more polite.
What?
Stay frosty, team.
I used to eat punks like this for breakfast.
Jehovah's witness!
I'm sorry, I just zoned out for a second.
Did you say that we're going up against five gangsters?
And bouncer makes six.
And three-quarters.
What the fuck do you want?
Good evening, young man. We'd like a word with Jimmy Kim.
If it's not too inconvenient.
Get the fuck out of here before I tear your head off, you old fuck.
I'm sorry.
I think we're in trouble.
I just don't understand why people feel the need, to use that kind of language.
Whoa!
There he goes.
Oh, sweet Jesus.
Battle Guy, what did I tell you about taking the Lord's name in vain?
Sorry, sir.
Eisenhower, at the ready.
Insect Man, I want you right behind me.
Everybody else spread out, catch the strays.
Oh.
And try to have fun,
otherwise what's the point?
Nice party. Anybody wanna dance?
Where are you going?
-Very nice.     -Behind you!
Watch the birdie.
Whoo!
Don't you move.
Night Bitch! Behind you!
Wait.
Look out!
Okay, I got his right arm.
You know, you shouldn't talk with your mouth full.
It's very rude. Come on.
Who the hell are you?
We're the good guys.
Oh, no, you're the fucking dead guys.
Eisenhower! Schwantz!
Oh!
Ow!
Where are the girls?
Come on, man. I've got a heart problem.
Oh, yeah?
No.
Do you want me to solve that for you?
Whoa, whoa!
Okay. The girls are upstairs in the apartments.
My little brother, he's on the till. He's just a college kid.
-Kick-Ass, Night Bitch.     -On it.
Ralph D'Amico is gonna end you for this.
Ow! It hurts!
Yeah, there's a dog on your balls.
You want money? There's 50 grand on the table.
Please just make him stop! Please!
You think you can buy us? Is that what you think?
We're not here to steal from you.
We're here to send a message to all the other bottom-dwellers.
-We're shutting you down.     -Come on.
There's a van waiting outside from a battered women's shelter.
It'll take you some place safe.
-Go. Go.     -We really can't leave.
We have no money.
Battle Guy, how much they have on the table?
Oh, it's like 50 grand.
You got plenty now.
Thank you.
Good job, guys.
Very tidy. Very tidy.
I can't believe you pulled a gun on that guy.
Were you really gonna shoot him?
Let you in on a little secret.
Empty. Don't tell the bad guys.
Pardon my language, Colonel, but you have got some serious balls.
Certainly more than Mr. Kim.
"There's a dog on my balls."
God damn it.
-Javier!     -What happened?
Some douche just posted a link to a story about a whorehouse,
says that Kick-Ass' team took them out.
What the hell? Where's my crew?
Chris, everybody's just...
Uh, can you ladies excuse us for a second?
Uh, no, they're my sidekicks. They can listen to what we have to say.
They're not your sidekicks, Chris.
They're prostitutes and witnesses, come on.
-All right.     -Sorry, no offense.
Everybody's just too afraid of your Uncle Ralph to take the job.
But he's in prison.
Doesn't matter. He runs the family now.
And he wants everybody to lay low.
But, fortunately for you,
Big Tony doesn't know how to lay low, so he's in.
-I don't remember a Big Tony. Is he huge?     -He's ironic.
5 foot 4, but mean as shit.
He's got such a hard-on for killing people.
-He's little and he kills.     -Right.
Call him "The Tumor."
Who's next?
All right, we've got, uh, an ex-Triad member looking for work.
Easy, "Genghis Carnage." Come on.
You gotta quit with the racist stereotypes, Chris.
Archetypes. Keep going.
We got, uh, Katarina Dumbrovski.
Wait, wait. A chick?
Yeah.
Seriously, you hired a chick?
Yeah. Former KGB.
She was locked up in the Gulag until she ate her cellmate.
Okay. "Mother Russia."
Mother Russia and Motherfucker both on the same team?
That doesn't work, Chris.
I am not asking for suggestions, asshole.
Just get them costumes and get them ready!
Shit.
Javier, thank you.
I couldn't do this without you.
You're pretty much like the only real family I have left.
Not a problem, man. I got your back.
It's kinda like you're the Alfred to my evil Bruce Wayne.
Did you just call me your fucking butler?
Yeah, is that not a compliment?
Shit. My bad.
There wasn't much action most nights.
I mean, there was always a little action with Night Bitch.
The reality of being a superhero is lots of patrols.
But that didn't stop people from begging to join up.
With all our new members,
it seemed kinda shitty not to ask Todd.
Stop peeking, man, you're gonna ruin it.
Check it out.
You can't fight crime in that.
Your pants are so tight, you got frog-eye.
What the hell's "frog-eye"?
-Male camel toe.     -What?
I'm not really sure about these names, either.
"Whup-Ass," "Kick-Ass-Man."
-"Dr. Kick-Ass"?     -Yeah.
Yeah, they all kinda seem derivative.
Let me translate that.
You can't just copy Dave's name, you knob-gobbler.
Okay. Um...
Uh...
Oh, wait. Oh, I got it.
I got it. I got it.
"Ass Kicker."
Seriously?
You're such a dick, Marty.
I know this is why you guys aren't texting me back,
I'm not an actual idiot.
Well, you could have fooled me, Ass-Licker.
-Yeah, well, screw you guys.     -Todd...
No, really. Fuck you guys.
I'm gonna go find my own team.
Todd. Wait. Come on.
Todd was right, we were being dicks.
But the truth is, the only person
I really wanted on the team was Mindy,
but she was too busy trying not to be a superhero.
Okay, Min, he's here.
Your first big date. How are you feeling?
Like the first time Big Daddy sent me into
a crack den with nothing but a penknife.
I've got some butterflies.
You just be yourself and you let me be nervous.
Don't worry about me. I can kill a man with his own finger.
A word of advice, I wouldn't open with that.
Thanks for letting me finally take you out.
Well, uh,
how else was I gonna get you to stop calling?
-Thanks.     -You're welcome.
Where are we going?
To a party.
Why is this party in the middle of nowhere?
Because that's where keg parties usually are, right?
Guess we're the first ones here.
This isn't where you have a party, moron.
This is where you dump a dead body.
What's your problem?
I'm sorry.
I'll stop being such a bitch.
You actually seem like a nice guy.
So, um...
you wanna hook up?
And a total idiot.
Simon, get back in the car.
Now!
Yay, you made it.
Brooke?
This is to celebrate you.
Celebrate?
What a total loser you are.
And we ditch losers.
Poor Mindy. What did you think?
The cool kids saw something special in you
and invited you to your first party
where you'd sip your first beer
and finally suck face for the first time?
Newsflash, you're not special.
Fuck with the queen bee and you're gonna get stung.
Date ditch.
Party at my house!
Pathetic.
Simon, you can drive us.
Dave?
Oh, my God! Mindy?
Holy shit. What are you doing?
Just needed to see my Robin, I guess.
Are you okay?
Hey, hey, hey.
I don't know what to do.
Those girls, they're...
they're evil.
It's just high school. Who gives a shit?
You should be out there in the real world making it a better place.
Dave, I can't.
I know, you promised your dad.
But he's not here anymore.
This is your life. You've gotta live it.
How am I supposed to face them tomorrow?
I'm so embarrassed.
Why?
You're smart. You're beautiful. You're funny.
You're the strongest person I've ever met. You can do anything.
And you're Hit Girl.
Doesn't matter if you're wearing a mask or makeup,
it's who you really are.
So what should I do? Cut their tongues out?
No! Definitely not.
I'm fucking with you.
Just beat them at their own game.
By being yourself.
Well, if you really wanna be popular,
consider two little words, "sex," "tape".
Lois, you don't need these ax wounds.
If I can dress like them, so can you.
It's a gift from some drug dealer who went missing.
Just because you dress like us,
doesn't mean you can be like one of us.
It doesn't matter what costume I wear, yours or mine,
I'm a superhero. That's who I am.
Okay, Captain Muffin-Muncher,
have fun playing make-believe.
This?
This is all make-believe, Brooke.
The reality is you're an evil bitch
who's just as bad as the worst criminal scum.
You wanna get real, Mindy?
In the real world, I win.
I go to an awesome college, I marry a hot guy
and I make adorable
babies for my nanny to take care of while we vacay in Paris.
My life is gonna rock and yours is gonna suck.
And no matter how slutty you dress,
no boy is ever gonna wanna kiss that hole you call a mouth.
So why don't you spare us all the whining and slit your wrists now?
'Cause the only thing that's gonna ruin my day
is looking at your face one more second.
-Told her.     -Damn.
What's that? A ghetto cell phone?
Gonna call for help with a come-back? Hmm.
Actually,
my daddy bought this from a disgruntled DARPA employee.
You see, it was designed for crowd control, but deemed too severe.
It emits a pulse that creates spontaneous nausea and diarrhea.
He called it "the sick stick."
Either your daddy got ripped off,
or you're back in make-believe land, sweetheart,
because we feel fabulous.
Not for long.
Oh, my God!
You get away from me. Please, you win.
I don't wanna win. I just want to make the world a better place.
Dad?
You home? Dad?
Is this what you've been up to while I'm out working nights saving for your college?
You've been dressing up and fighting people?
There is blood on these stick things.
What are you doing in my room?
I was looking for drugs.
I was worried about you.
Okay, good. Now you can stop.
No. Now I'm even more worried.
Jesus, Dave, drugs would have been better.
This is deranged.
Whoa. Some people do a lot worse.
Oh, the people you hang out with?
No. The people I hang out with are superheroes.
There is no such thing, Dave.
This is the real world with real consequences.
When are you gonna grow up?
If it means turning into you, never.
I don't wear the mask because I'm ashamed of who I am.
Not like you.
What's that supposed to mean?
If you're not at work, you're here doing crunches.
Why? So you can look like someone else?
Maybe get a few more years of doing nothing?
Your life has no meaning, Dad.
When you're gone, who's gonna notice?
Where the hell are you going?
Oh, uh, I'm leaving. That's what you do when you grow up.
Did he say why he wanted to see me?
When your Uncle Ralph calls, I don't ask questions.
Just the kid.
Chris, just be cool and you'll be fine.
Hey, how you doing?
Good, Uncle Ralph.
Listen, Chrissy, things have been tough all around since your dad,
you know.
Well, I been trying to get the family back on track from in here.
They record these things.
I know, it's fine.
The warden's a pal. Now listen to me.
It's okay to have a bit of fun,
but you can't go hiring a gang of heavy hitters.
Javier should have told you.
No, it doesn't matter.
Uncle Ralph, I am gonna make Kick-Ass pay for what he did to us.
Chrissy, you need to forget that punk.
It's more important that you stay out of this.
You're not like me, or your dad, you're, uh...
special.
You can't tell me what to do anymore.
I know who I am now.
Oh, yeah?
And who's that?
The Motherfucker.
You think you're the big bad guy, huh?
Let me show you what real evil looks like.
Hello?
Javier, what's going on?
Chris, what's up?
What are you doing on Lou's phone, huh?
Drop yours in the toilet again?
Everything okay?
Thank you for that. I needed it.
For what comes next.
Don't be stupid, Chris.
Just get out of town for a while. Go to college or something.
Why? You just taught me everything I needed to know.
Voila!
Presto and elegant, damn. Them boys designed a very tasty logo.
What's the matter, girl? You hear something?
Come on, let's go see. Come on!
Anybody out here?
I don't see anything.
Gonna have to stay in there until you calm down, you lunatic.
I wonder what's bothering you.
I know. Tonight you die.
Ladies first.
You will not shoot me.
You are superhero.
You help people. You do not hurt them.
That's supervillain territory.
Or as I like to call my little gang,
the Toxic Mega-Cunts.
Hi.
Yeah, like your head.
Yay!
Ooh, it's gotta hurt!
I did my homework on you, Colonel.
You used to be Sal Bertolini, didn't you?
Did a few jobs for my dad back in the day, before you got "born again."
I used to hang with a lot of losers.
Is this how you thought you'd die, Sal?
Dressed like an idiot?
Who are you supposed to be?
I'm The Motherfucker!
And I'm here to end Kick-Ass. Not just kill him.
I am gonna shit on everything that he loves.
Let's trash this place, guys.
"Miranda Swedlow"?
Who's that, Sal? She one of the whores on your team?
Night Bitch all snuggled up to Kick-Ass.
Looks like our boy's got a new hot pocket.
Want me to kill his dog?
The dog? Jesus Christ, I'm not that evil.
Cut the old man's head off.
You guys hungry? I'm starving. Come on.
Pizza, can we get pizza?
We're getting pizza.
Don't worry, I kill you first.
Justice For...
ever.
A Brooklyn resident was found decapitated last night.
According to Twitter, a man claiming to be
the world's first supervillain...
I told you, no TV. You're grounded, remember?
Marcus, I know I made you a promise,
but I can't keep being someone I'm not.
When I see evil, I have to stop it.
Mindy, what you did to those girls at school was unacceptable.
-You could have really hurt them.     -You're right, I could have,
but instead I sent them home with tummy-aches.
Boo-fucking-hoo.
I don't get it. This obsession that you have with revenge is not healthy.
If you don't let me and the police do our jobs,
there is gonna be nothing that I can do for you.
You're never gonna have a normal life
and you'll probably end up like your father.
Marcus, they cut a guy's head off.
Who else is going to stop them?
Kick-Ass? You?
You go to your room and do your homework.
Now!
Hey, guys, we're signing a sympathy card for the Colonel's sister.
You wanna go 5 bucks each so we can send flowers from the team?
Did you guys see The Motherfucker's Twitter page?
Who is this guy? And what's his problem with us?
I don't know, but he has got some elephant-sized balls.
He's been bragging on the web about what they did to the Colonel.
Can that be traced?
I tried. His IP address is masked.
All right, here's what we're gonna do. We're gonna organize a fight.
There are a lot of guys online who said they're in if we need them.
Are you kidding me? This isn't West Side Story.
We didn't join up to be in a gang.
We did this so we could help people.
Shannon's right. We need to leave this to the cops.
We better start walking in pairs.
Motherfucker's tweeted that the Colonel was just the beginning.
Anybody seen Night Bitch?
Are you sure she's on that team?
Stupid gash posted on her superhero page that
she's dating Kick-Ass.
So, yeah, I'm damn sure.
Hello, Night Bitch!
Hey.
Oh, she wants to take the party upstairs.
We're gonna have a party.
She closed the door.
Don't worry, darling, I'm not gonna kill you.
I want you to give a message to your boyfriend.
Come on, wriggly.
Let go!
You're done banging superheroes, baby.
It's time to see what evil dick feels like.
Shit.
What's wrong?
What are you doing?
Come on!
God, okay, I'm just... I'm not in the mood.
I guess evil dick feels limp.
Hurt her. Bad!
Cops are coming.
Leave it to Mother Russia.
She makes 10 times what we do.
Fifty thousand a week. Plus expenses.
Hey, watch out!
Wow!
Reverse it! Reverse it!
Don't move! Freeze!
Fifty thousand. She's worth it.
Whoa, whoa! Why are they backing up?
Why is there a lawnmower on the trunk?
Wow!
We need back-up, eight men down.
I think you mean 10.
Let's bounce!
Put the word out I'm building an evil army.
All psychopaths and ex-cons welcome.
I don't think you're gonna have a problem when people hear about this.
They just disappeared?
All they have to do is take off their masks,
no one's gonna recognize them once they're back in their street clothes.
Your attention, please!
Feds traced the IP addresses for all those other costumed freaks.
We got every law enforcement agency
in the state working to hit them at once!
Why is Kick-Ass on this list?
His crew does community service.
I don't give a shit. Anyone wearing a mask is getting detained.
We're putting an end to this tonight!
A lot of people said the cops were too heavy-handed that night.
But you gotta put it into context.
The police didn't mind our real life superhero stuff
as long as we were picking up litter
or helping old ladies cross the street.
But suddenly it was serious.
Suddenly we represented everything that was wrong with society.
Freeze!
Dad had warned me that the real world had real consequences.
As they pulled up, he must have been feeling pretty damn vindicated.
Oh, shit, Dave. What have you done?
Police, open up.
Hey.
Hi.
Uh, uh, it's me, Kick-Ass.
Wow.
You're actually pretty cute under that mask.
I'm so sorry about what happened.
Don't be.
It's my own fault.
We're gonna find these assholes and make this right.
What's the point?
I mean, we're really superheroes
about as much as we're really dating.
We don't even know each other's names.
I think it's time to get back to the real world.
I thought we were trying to make it a better place.
Then why is it worse?
Maybe Night Bitch was right,
which means Dad was, too.
I mean, things had gotten out of hand.
Maybe it was time for me to stop crashing at Marty's
and start apologizing.
Dad?
Whoa, whoa. That's my dad.
Your dad's Kick-Ass? What?
Yeah, he just gave himself up.
You don't understand. He's doing this to protect me.
Dad!
-Mindy?     -Dave?
I need your help. My dad's been arrested.
They think he's Kick-Ass.
Can you talk to Marcus?
-I'm grounded.     -So?
So that means I can't get involved.
-Look. Wait a second.     -I wish I could help.
Mindy! Are you on the phone?
Look, I gotta go, okay?
I'm sorry, Dave.
Mindy, wait, wait.
Hey, what the hell were you thinking?
Yeah, I could ask you the same thing.
I can't believe you lied to them.
I wasn't gonna do nothing while you went to jail.
I chose this. You should let me deal with the consequences.
I thought you wanted me to grow up.
Yeah? When you get a kid of your own one day, you'll understand.
I'm gonna tell them the truth.
No. Hey... It'll just make things worse.
Look, I spoke to my attorney.
He said they gotta let me out by tomorrow.
No actual crime was committed.
There are people out there who wanna kill Kick-Ass.
Well, the cops are out there looking for them,
so the safest place for Kick-Ass is right here, locked away.
I don't know how you got into all this shit, but
you gotta promise me you will never dress up in that outfit again.
Do you hear me?
I promise.
This evil lair owns!
Do people still say that, "own"?
Yeah, of course.
Your shark. Something's wrong.
Think you used the wrong kind of water.
What the hell, Eyal?
It's fine, Chris. They're supposed to lie at the bottom of the tank.
It's just their way of, how you say, settling into their environment.
Don't screw me on this, okay?
You said we'd be ready in two days,
we don't even have a men's room yet.
Don't worry.
What's with the bags of shit?
It's fertilizer for the bombs.
You're not a Supervillain if you don't have a plan to destroy the city.
It will not work. You need a chemical kind.
Do I have to do everything myself?
Just fix it!
You must relax. Everything is going as planned.
Mmm, no. No. Except it's not, okay?
That sad sack is not Kick-Ass.
I've seen Kick-Ass, he's like my age.
Guy's old enough to be his father.
No shit, right.
I'm sorry, who are you?
I... uh, volunteered for your evil army, like the others.
Right. I appreciate that. Thanks for joining the cause.
This is the VIP area for the core group.
I just thought it was funny you said that.
Because he is Kick-Ass' father.
Who?
Mr. Lizewski. He's Kick-Ass' dad.
Shut up!
Yeah. You're not gonna tell anyone, are you?
No.
But you, my friend, have just earned life-time access to my VIP area.
Go take a little seat.
Hey, get the kid a Frappuccino,
then put his little punk ass back to work.
Okay.
Come on.
Can I help you?
The Motherfucker wants us to take a picture with you.
It helps that my dad is a really good lawyer.
Because I don't think my beautiful ass
would last too long in prison.
Whoa, that's weird. Chris D'Amico just texted me a picture.
Red Mist? Whatever happened to that guy?
What is it?
Dude, what's wrong?
The next few days passed in a fog.
It didn't matter that I told the police about Chris,
they couldn't find him.
The cops did show up at Dad's funeral,
not out of respect,
but because they were scared something would happen.
My dad was a decent man.
All he ever did was try and give me a good life,
and I told him no one would notice when he was gone.
I love you, pal.
I love you, too, Dad.
You guys came.
We'd love to help you track down this Chris D'Amico d-bag, but
we just got out on parole.
No, that's fine.
I'm not looking for revenge.
Last thing I promised my dad was that I was gonna give this up.
That's exactly what I'm gonna do.
But you started this.
Now I'm ending it.
Dave, I'm so sorry. Do you hate me for not helping?
No, not even a little bit.
You were right. You gave it up.
If I had, too, my dad would still be alive.
The only person I blame is myself.
Let's do this!
Get down!
Mindy!
Spread out!
Keep your head down!
Come on!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Get him!
Get that van over here!
Hurry up!
Mindy?
Mindy!
You gotta put this on.
I'm not gonna do it.
There's nothing left you can do to hurt me.
You wanna bet?
Whoa! Whoa!
Game on, cocksuckers!
There's a girl on the roof!
She's still up there!
-I think I got her!     -Go check!
Get out there!
Come on! Move your head.
Pull over, pube-face.
We know Chris D'Amico is The Motherfucker.
Where is he hiding?
Eat a dick.
You're gonna eat yours if you don't start talking.
Go ahead and shoot me, you little bitch.
There's nothing you can do that would make me talk.
Look, hold on. I can't do this right now. It's my dad's funeral.
Dave, your father loved you.
Just like my daddy loved me. And I know it hurts, but maybe,
maybe that's the real meaning of being a superhero.
Is taking that pain and turning it into something good.
Something right.
Remember what you told me?
This is your life. You've gotta live it.
Now help me find some pliers. I'm gonna make this guy eat his own dick.
Seriously?
-Hello?     -Marcus?
Mindy. What's going on? Are you okay?
I'm fine.
We know where The Motherfucker's hiding.
He's recruiting an army of supervillains and making homemade bombs.
Marcus, he wants to burn the city down.
You promised me.
I know you see me as this little girl,
but I'm not and I never was.
You're right.
Daddy did take my childhood away,
but I'm not so sure that was a bad thing.
Marcus, he gave me a gift,
a gift that I can't escape no matter how hard I try.
And I don't need to spend the next four years of my life
trying to figure out who I am
because I already know.
I'm Hit Girl.
I posted the address. Do you think they'll show?
Chris has an army.
These real life super dweebs have been waiting their whole lives for a call like this.
Are you okay?
What? Yeah, no... I'm fine.
Here.
Take this.
"Last resort" really isn't my style.
Dave, this isn't a comic book.
Real people are going to die tonight.
My daddy was prepared for anything.
Are you?
Yeah.
I am.
They should be back by now!
It's definitely dead.
Says on the Internet you're supposed to keep them in fresh water.
It is just hungry. We must feed it.
Why are you looking at me?
We gotta get this shit started.
Oh, yeah. Have I got a show for you bitches!
Motherfucker, Motherfucker...
All right, party people!
We are gonna kill Kick-Ass,
the very first superhero, together.
We are gonna cut him up into little pieces,
feed that shit to MC Shark
and post it all over YouTube. For real!
He's kidding, right?
Motherfucker don't kid.
That's not it. I'm gonna give each and every one of you
party favor fertilizer bombs!
And we are gonna get our riot on!
That's what it means to be evil.
We, my friends, are the real 1%,
and tonight we are gonna fuck this city up or my name is not...
Chris D'Amico!
That is not my name!
No, you're right. Your new name's Little Bitch.
Oh, this is perfect.
Are you really that stupid?
There's two of you and a whole army of us.
Do you really have such a hard-on to die?
No.
That's why we brought our friends.
What's the matter, Chris? Shit hit your shorts?
Yeah, and I'm gonna wipe my ass with your face.
You're gonna pay for what you did to my dad.
Your dad? You blew up my dad with a bazooka.
Oh!
Are you ready to die, little girl?
I might be if I have to keep looking at that shit-stain you call a face.
Chris!
Hold him down. I wanna see what his guts look like.
That's enough from you boys!
Nicely done, sweetheart.
That all you got?
No, I got my lethal zero G device.
Bullshit.
No shit.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Thanks. Ass Kicker.
Nice.
Jesus, you are such a pussy.
What is the point of wearing a mask if you can't do what you want?
We want to do good.
No, people want to win the lottery.
People want to fuck Scarlett Johansson.
You think you can kill me with little needle?
That's not what it's for.
It's called adrenaline, bitch.
What was that, some cheap shot?
That was for the Colonel.
Ahh!
That's for Night Bitch.
And that's for my dad.
What the hell are you doing?
Saving your whiny ass!
No!
I won't let you have this. I'd rather die!
What is wrong with you, dude? This is not a comic book, it's real life!
When you're dead, it's done. There's no sequel.
You made this real. You started it!
And I'm gonna finish it.
I'll be immortal, like an evil Jesus.
Wait!
I'm alive.
Dave, I'm so sorry.
The feeling was indescribable.
Chris D'Amico, dead.
His wannabe supervillains, defeated.
But did we make the world a better place?
Or did we just finish something
that began when I first put on this mask?
The cops are coming.
They'll take care of the bad guys.
We better skedaddle before they get here.
We did it.
Fuck, yeah.
Hey, language.
You're right, if we're gonna dress like heroes, we should act like heroes.
He'd be proud of you, Dave.
He'd be proud of all of us.
You know we can never do this again, right?
It's over.
One last time. Come on.
What do you say, Hit Girl? Are you in?
Why the hell not?
Justice Forever!
Thanks for the ride.
I'll see you at school.
I'm leaving New York, Dave.
I can't go home. I can't put Marcus in that position.
Why? He won't arrest you.
You just saved the city.
Yeah, well, I also killed six guys with a cop's gun.
Vigilantes don't get a free pass.
You can't go. People need you.
-They've got you now.     -Mindy...
I'm not like you.
You don't have to be a bad-ass to be a superhero, Dave.
You just have to be brave.
What was that?
That was my first kiss.
Be nice
or I'll rip your ass out through your mouth.
When Mindy left,
that's when I finally understood where my life was going.
Just like it had to eventually happen,
that real people would try to be superheroes.
Eventually it had to end, too.
Superheroes can't exist in the real world
for a reason.
It's because the real world needs real heroes.
And not some punk in a wet-suit playing dress-up,
but a genuine bad-ass who can really kick ass.
Hello?
Please. Don't go.
Don't go.
Is anybody there?
Hello?
Some help, please?
A shark bit my fucking dick off and I can't get some water?
特攻联盟２
稍早前…
同一时间…
城市的另一边…
约在包利街墨菲酒吧后门
你爸爸会希望你来的
因为我爸，所以我才不能参加什么团体
你不懂的，掰
罚钱罐
当夜稍晚…
跟你10元
老大，外面有人
我花钱不是请你来打手枪的
到你了
有没有搞错啊…
纽约市立看守所
所有超级英雄请注意，我们需要你
还以为你这个王八蛋多耐操
别走 后面还有
手枪子弹时速超过700哩
绝对不可能，你想太多了，不行
没问题，我不喜欢勉强别人
很好，别射我
没差
靠！我还活着
哦!
太神奇了！
对吧，所以…
嗯
再来一次？
死都不要
没差
说‘没差’却开枪射我胸口
麦搁闹啊
我超不爽
算了，小孬孬
我一直纳闷之前怎么没有超级英雄
其实是有的，那就是明蒂麦奎迪
她爸死后…
以前的同事马库斯成了监护人
-她拿粉红色小马背包？  -真可爱
谢谢
从幼稚园偷来的？
马库斯每天送她上学
他前脚一走，她后脚开溜
老师没发现
因为她骇进学校伺服器
还颁给自己全勤奖
超杀女和大老霸才真是狠角色
明蒂的宿命
就是终结罪恶
但无论撂倒多少毒枭
她依然难掩孤单
至于我?我不太想当超级英雄
因为实在太危险了
但问题是…我会无聊死
我就像一般高中生
不清楚人生方向
干，连想看哪一台都不知道
只是看个电视，又不是在说中东问题
我的麻吉陶德和马堤完全不知道…
我就是那红透半边天的元祖超级英雄
昨晚有看蜘蛛人吗？
我看到梅姨竟然会硬奇怪吧？
有恋祖情结的就不怪了
不是万圣节他们也变装
他们是正港的超级英雄…
自从第一位市民穿起超人装
这两年来…
大家已经开始争相效仿
我是因为屌爆侠所以才变身超级英雄
下班回家不久…
就整装待发，外出巡逻
帮大家维护社区安全
我激励了大家走上街头
自己却宅在家里
所以那天晚上吃饱
我就把超人装拿了出来
-抱歉  -哇!你不会敲门吗？
你要知道抚摸自己是很正常的
天呀，爸，给我出去！
如果我真的要考虑屌爆侠的复出
我就应该认真一点
可以聊聊吗？
明蒂拜托？
快上车，还在跳表
我想像蝙蝠侠、罗宾一样组个团队
没人想演罗宾
罗宾哪里不好？
你不就像大老霸身边的罗宾？
罗宾还恨不得是我咧
我想说的是，我们应该成为伙伴
你和我，就像二重奏一样
我都进了大联盟，你还在打少棒
所以呢？你可以训练我
我想当真正的英雄
而你几乎已经算是超级英雄了
单打独斗不累吗？
你难道不想找些伙伴？
可以能帮你分担的人？
我说什么你都照做？
当然
揍我
你才15岁…
搞屁呀？
小孬孬只有挨打的份
哇靠
明蒂像男生的‘朝旗’…
连续三周照三餐打我
防守！左、右，防守！
就算我末梢神经受损
依然生不如死
不过很怪，我挺爽的
总算找到努力的目标
-你的脸怎么了？  -没什么
仿佛朝着什么目标迈进
哇靠！
你太猛了！
其他人都在假扮超级英雄
但我们是要成为真正的英雄
我必须瞒着女友凯蒂、马堤与陶德
但我不再意，因为这太好玩了
左、右、左！
我们是超级英雄联盟
啥咪咙无惊
搞什么，妈？你删掉我录的新闻？
对，我做的，克里斯多夫
那是屌爆侠的新闻
克里斯多夫，别再追那个超级英雄了
他不是超级英雄，他是杀人凶手
他用火箭炮杀了爸爸，你醒醒
爸是火烧死的
火？你有问题吗？
你！你才是我的问题！
我一直希望你能成为一个正常的小孩
所以我才在你爸的意外后，搬到长岛
火箭筒才不是意外
你这个智障老太婆！
别说了
很好，我要走了
拜托！哈维尔，上道一点
抱歉，可是你妈请我不是因为我上道
我恨你！在家自修就像坐牢一样
你还丢掉赤雾侠的服装
妈的，我没有病，你才有！
我-要-你-嗝-屁！
妈？
别碰
抱歉，那是什么？
最后的武器…在你快死的时候用
你不怕…死吗？
你不怕你再也长不高了吗？
我是说真的
就算是蜘蛛人或蝙蝠侠也会死
如果你怕死，只有一件事是确定的
你死定了
我爸从来不怕死
他的下场不也是…
他知道总有一天要做出最终的牺牲
所以要我发誓
继续扞卫这座城市
如有违背
不得好死
你爸是疯子，你知道吧？
你错了，戴夫
我爸才是第一个正港超级英雄
你和赤雾侠都不是，我爸才是
为他做事真的很光荣
明蒂，今天上学好玩吗？
超疯的
今天穆林老师休假，库柏先生代课
无聊到爆
怪了，因为校长昨天打电话来说
你要领全勤奖
却从没有来上课
我跟踪你，却发现你和一个男生上车
后来在桥上跟丢了
可以告诉我去了哪里吗？
对不起，我不是故意惹你生气
别假哭了，你15岁了，不是5岁
我说了
他要我跷课，一起去逛购物中心
所以我就去了
这和超杀女无关吧？
我不会在床底下发现飞刀和飞镖吧？
不会的，我只是希望他喜欢我
跷课不是求爱的好方法
-我真笨  -嘿，嘿
你是最聪明的小女孩，去吃披萨吧
我不用被禁足吗？
这次先记警告
真的想丢光你妈的遗物？
不然要怎么处理她的鬼东西？
哇靠，她有一对…
老兄，她死了，别再肖想她的奶子
我是说这个
天哪，那是我爸的
何不自己留着？
可以吗？
当然，这是你的了
听着，克里斯…你现在是当家的
-小心一点就好，知道吗？  -灾啦
哇!
你绝对不想要这个！
我来处理
你今天先回家吧，再见
嘿
准备好第一波实战演练了没？
这些要干嘛？
穿上…然后去钓鱼
没有皮条客像我这么白
听好了，下一条街右转
从弗莱布许大道出来
不扮屌爆侠没关系吗？
这才是重点
屌爆侠不是一套服装，而是真实的你
戴夫莱佐斯基才是你的面具
看来我的‘面具’要被打惨了
死Gay炮，这些袋子干嘛的？
说你要拿12寸的按摩棒捅他老母
我只是在散步
这不是我的作风，我都直接找警察
你在跟谁说话？
我只是在讲电话
这里的收讯…烂透了
袋子给我，死娘炮
别逼我让你吸大屌
快点
好啦，好啦
这几周来我让明蒂扁到痛哭流涕
就是为了再来这里挨打
搞什么鬼
想死吗？死娘炮！
你们一直讲那些屁话，看起来更娘
手下留情…
再让我发现你抢劫…你这个屎汉堡
我就会扯爆你菊花再砍断你的脏手
答应我再也不做坏事了
我答应你
鬼才信
-怎么样？  -你差点害死我
不是啦，我是说我的台词
‘鬼才信’我想了一大堆
快走！我会说你救了我，走吧！
女性嫌犯逃离弗莱布许大道
不到5尺，蒙面，手持双节棍和剑
-明蒂  -马库斯，怎么了？
你接了电话
表示你不在学校
我…
我不舒服，所以护士决定叫我回家
真可怜，我快到家了
等下煮个汤，一起看‘百万小学堂’
好啊，待会见罗
待会见
糟了!
我的汤呢？
让我看你有没有发烧
流真多汗
睡一下就会好了
先休息一下，我去煮汤
那是血吗？
为什么骗我，我不会再放任你了
我和你爸情同兄弟
他是好警察也是英雄
但大老霸呢？他不是你爸
他剥夺了你的童年
还有这个…
超杀女？也不是真正的你
你是明蒂麦奎迪，刚上高中
你现在还不认识真正的自己
但你会的，只要去尝试
我不想
你不知道自己想要什么
你还小，还太早
我15年来的经历，已经胜过很多大人
你爸留下的纸条
就是他死后我们才看的那张
写了什么？
你会照顾我
你应该听我的话，对吧？
你听好
我希望你上学，别再跟那个男生来往
你还要答应我
别再发生这种事
如有违背
不得好死
很好
明蒂！
怎么了？
你先害我差点没命，然后搞失踪
戴夫，对不起
我…真的？
没错
我真的很对不起
好吧，随便你
我是说…你不像是会道歉的人
你要我讲几遍？
我们走吧
今天别太大力，我好像肋骨断了
我不干了
今天不想训练？
什么都不干了
等一下，你是说…全部？
不行，你可是超杀女
不是才要组团，你怎么能一走了之
放弃你的宿命
再也不是了，戴夫
对不起，可是结束了，我不干了
刚才她是在跟他分手?
别理我了
不要再跟我道歉了
到底是哪个比较恶心，是跟国中生上床
-还是被国中生甩了？  -哇，哇!
恋童癖
不是这样的
不然呢？请告诉我
我不能说，这和屌爆侠有关
我也有事情瞒着你，记得马利克吗？
针具交换站的志工？
他的‘棒子’比屌爆侠…大上好几倍
-骗人  -是真的
我说的‘棒子’是屌
我懂，谢了
睡过15岁是要坐20年牢的，变态
跟国三的搞？有够坏的
有问题嘛？毛都长了当然可以玩
当然不是
克里斯，家教来了
克里斯！
克里斯，你…
靠北，你干嘛穿成这样？
我的宿命
只因为你老母最近有点起肖？
我有我的宿命
我爸曾是黑道老大，这就说得通了
我会进化成超级坏蛋
快点
克里斯，把枪放下，免得伤到别人
我不是克里斯
好吧，赤雾侠…
赤雾侠是我以前当超级英雄的名字
从今以后，叫我…
臭B王
自从明蒂退出江湖…
我决定不再练拳，直接上街巡逻
屌爆侠，欢迎回来！
-耶!  -哇!
你是最屌的！
唯一的问题是，我依然孤军奋战
所以我上网找到一个物理教授
他自称‘重力博士’
他当然比不上超杀女，但聊胜于无
我发明的零重力装置
可以抬起一吨重的东西
真的假的？
这么好骗，这只是球棒包着锡箔纸
你还是上当了
我要一罐健怡汽水
我甚至不是物理系教授
我只是在广告公司写文案的
这就是我喜欢的原因
我可以成为任何人
你经常打团体战？
算吧，不…其实没有
有人陪可以壮胆
我也这么想，我从来没有打过架
我也希望你不会碰到
我有个脸书朋友想组团
我不确定他有多认真
但他照片挺酷的
真的吗？这就是我联络你的原因
我不敢太早提出来，怕吓到你
我小个便就开他的档案给你看
你叔叔拉夫看到会生气的，克里斯
别叫我克里斯
我不会说你的新名字
你的老大起初是我爸
再来是我妈，现在换我
我大概是全纽约最有钱的小孩
看不惯就回家吃自己吧！
屌爆侠！
老兄，很高兴见到你
需要我帮忙吗？
帮我把影片点阅率冲破一百万
来吧，来吧
快跑，屌爆侠，快跑！
去你妈的纽泽西烂咖！
一对一就不行了吗？
那不算一对一，明天有聚会
地址再传给你
当心重力博士！
你忍不住佩服博士的热血
我超期待见到他的朋友
手举高，春卷先生
现金拿出来，别干蠢事
快点！摄影机在哪里？
-太贵了，这里没有  -不会吧？
恁娘咧！这样怎么出名？
你想被拍？
闭嘴，趴在地上！
你最好告诉大家‘臭B王’来过
你头壳坏掉吗，孩子？
你也趴着，甘道夫
不然就炸了你的屁眼
枪拿好，不然后座力会轰了你的脸
快趴在地上！
妈的，给我快一点！
我就说吧
走！快走！
发动车子！快走！
太爽了！
我觉得整个人都活起来了
我终于看清了我的宿命
我要摧毁全世界
让大家都知道臭B王！
找一些顶尖的综合格斗选手来训练我
譬如乔克李戴尔
我不在乎要花多少钱
我只想亲手杀了屌爆侠
这个值得推特一下
好罗，可以了吗？
不知道耶，我行吗？
你行的，你很漂亮
布鲁克人也很好
我要跟她们聊些什么？
我宁愿被刑求，也不要看小贾斯汀
-你会玩得很开心  -我会搞砸的
你又知道了？
因为那是他妈的睡衣派对
说脏话要罚钱
换大一点的吧
酷吧？这是用来运送啤酒的
老兄，你的地下总部竟然有秘密电梯
我跟你提过这间屋子的主人
这分明就是蝙蝠洞
-完全同意  -赞啦
这是我一生中看过最酷的时刻
欢迎加入正义永存联盟
威廉斯探员，这想必是明蒂
你猜对了
你们玩得开心点，早上再来接你
我会割腕自杀
不，你的指甲会修得漂漂亮亮
-是吗？  -相信我
女孩们，跟明蒂打招呼
嘿
我认识你
你就是骑过戴夫摇杆的国中生
我没有骑…
如果只是吹，那还能算处女
看她就知道她没吹过
那舔屁眼？打手枪？戳菊花？
天啊，至少有亲他吧？
当然
你从没亲过男生吧？
天呀！好可爱喔
说不定她是T婆
说不定我会踹你个鸡巴
她有够呛，我喜欢
有什么大不了
不过是喇舌而已
喇舌当然很爽
就像看Union J的MV时的感觉
不会吧，你不知道他们？
这个会改变你的世界
♬ 别说你很孤单，我来帮你分忧解劳 ♬
♬ 我会一直守候着你 ♬
你们比史丹李的男粉丝还疯吧？
谁是史丹李？
♬ 我会抱着你，我会抱着你 ♬
♬ 我会抱着你 ♬
♬ 你知道我会抱着你 ♬
♬ 你仿佛跑了几个小时 ♬
♬ 上气不接下气 ♬
♬ 恶魔在你脑中大声尖叫 ♬
♬ 你疲累了，你受伤了 ♬
♬ 你备受艰辛，你伤痕累累 ♬
♬ 但别想太多，只要撑住 ♬
♬ 我会抱着你 ♬
什么鬼东西？
对吧，我都湿了
这就是你
我们的穿着和谈吐也许不太一样
但说到男生，我们都哈到不行
暮光之城、查宁坦图、Union J
这是生物本能，小荡妇，别抗拒它
我…
我要走了
但我们要去罗根小屋哈草狂欢
我想给你班上女生抢破头的机会
你难道不想每天穿着紧身衣出门…
接受大家的膜拜？
你难道不想夜晚偷溜出去…大闹一场
让全世界知道
你是多么坚强独立？
你难道不渴望归属感？
♬ 你知道我会抱着你 ♬
我能穿这样去吗？
当然!
一定会很好玩
我们找过警察…也找过记者
甚至架过…那个什么…对，网站
请大家帮我们寻找汤米
呃…
但都没用，我们再也没有见到儿子
我就发起一个‘别忘了汤米’的活动
每周三次
星条旗上校从网路找到我们
你们太惨了，真的很遗憾
自从我妹遭到谋杀，弃尸垃圾桶后
我就化身暗夜骚货
天啊
虽然无法挽回她
至少对社会有帮助
-虫人换你  -是…
我是同性恋，一直受到霸凌…
现在我挺身为弱势发声
所以我不戴面具
不想再羞于见人
只要心存正义
谁管你嘴巴含什么
-击拳吧  -谢谢上校
我爸妈看完歌剧
回家遇袭身亡，我就变身单挑王
我有告诉过你们吗？
那家伙还在色情网站刷爆他们信用卡
希望我们会遇上他
我会亲自揍到他魂飞魄散
不会吧，马堤？
我认得你的声音
不，我听不懂你在说什么
我不认识马堤，新来的
混帐，是我，戴夫
戴夫？你干嘛扮成屌爆侠？
因为…我就是屌爆侠
你们认识？
对，五岁就认识了
你干嘛瞎掰父母遭到谋杀？
-别说脏话  -什么？
单挑王，不介意更新履历表吧？
呃…
我一直烦恼该怎么自我介绍…
才不会像个白痴
这大概很难，蝙蝠侠
我也这么想
呃…
当我遇见你们…
你们都超有故事的
星条旗上校，混过黑道，超神的
别妄称神的名
对不起
我想没有好故事
你就不会让我加入
这次放过你，单挑王
-想看酷的东西吗？  -想
这可以当成会议室
太酷了
我偷偷的完成改装
所以没人知道
目前还很阳春，但只是开始
我们可以一起改变世界
喔!
屌爆侠，如果你愿意加入我们
我们深感荣幸
当然啦！
我就是想听到这个
好啦，开炮了
背对我，裤子我来脱
什么？
玩笑话，干正事了
被耍了吧
找到你了
我们帮你留了位置
你都没来
我通常会去餐厅补充碳水化合物
我一岁以后就没吃过糖
你怕胖吗？
收小腹的秘诀就是参加舞蹈校队
报名表就在公布栏上
我还是不敢相信你就是屌爆侠
这就像好朋友的…
真实身份是威尔史密斯
你们好，聊些什么？
没什么
-没什么？  -对啊，陶德，随便聊
好吧，待会见
陶德，等一下
-小心  -小心我毙了你
算了
大概是臭B王的粉丝吧
谁?
臭B王？
他自称是全世界第一个超级坏蛋
目前有一千个粉丝
真是脑残
-来啊!  -哈!来吧!
臭B王，你没问题的！
他真的有可能赢吗？
不然就退钱
综合格斗就像下棋
战术才是关键
那小子没问题的
死期到了，俗辣
-没事吧？  -我很好
打得好，这拳真猛，老兄
放轻松，孩子，撑下去
-哦!  -可恶！
你打断我的腿！
-快想办法  -中场休息
是啊，暂停一下，伙计们，来吧
这么不小心啊，死娘泡！
恰克！把他拖走！
你太超过了
没事吧，老弟？
闪开，我要赢了
不，你哭了
你懂什么？算了，我的力量就是…
…他妈的有钱
想为我工作吗？
想帮我K人吗？
-想  -很好！
我们会提供面具和服装
你就叫…黑死病
你不觉得有点种族歧视吗？
那又怎样？
放话出去…
我重金募集镇上职业杀手
我们先谈一谈
有钱好办事
你希望我独立
我不就照做了？
-我再打电话问问  -好极了！
还有谁想成为超级坏蛋？
我保证比小屌哥乔克李戴尔付得多
你叫我什么？
他打到脑震荡，不知道自己在说什么
教练波德尔是我的私人家教
其实家教只是幌子
我妈贿赂她，让我加入校队
只要表现不要太差，我保证你可以
至少可以当候补队员
你会帮我？
姐妹淘分什么彼此
如果布鲁克想养宠物，她应该买只狗
明蒂只是她的最新嗜好
各位同学，找位置坐，要开始了
明蒂麦奎迪？
别紧张，只要不摔倒，你就过关了
去吧
四个坏蛋
无路可逃
你简直可以当队长了
布鲁克差远了
天啊
布鲁克没机会当队长了
一群人取了假名…
穿着自制服装
上网搜寻悬案
漫画英雄都有造价几十亿的基地
以及月球总部，但这是真实世界
-…分阶段，红白蓝  -真酷
-那是什么？  -砖块
然后呢
-怎么样？  -挺不错的
人民应该过着更好的生活
游民应该吃到热呼呼的食物
酒醉女大生应该安全返家
至于变态和恋童癖…
就应该见一见艾森豪
‘德语’
鸡鸡！
好痛
你不会想用拳头的
因为骨头可能会断掉，你就无法防守
你要用迎面掌…换边…迎面掌…换边
抓住颈后…
我没参加过足球校队…
也没演过校内话剧
我连资优生也没当过
死了吧，贱货!
如果我曾经风光过…
大概就是这种感觉吧
当警察再也无法提供保护时…
抢劫犯和性变态你们给我听好
我们有力量，我们有胆量
帮助需要的人，给他们应得的一切！
正义永存！
我们是一个终极团队
大家不认识我们没关系
我们知道就够了，我们就像超级巨星
-晚安，伙计们  -干得漂亮，单挑王
晚安，上校，感谢你所做的一切
没什么，孩子，谢谢你
你让大家明白，人人都可以改变世界
没有屌爆侠，就没有我们
这都是真心话，但别自我膨胀
现在呢？
我还不会很累
嗯
嗯?
好吧
别摘下面具
-真的？  -真的
好吧!
今晚有大任务…
而且不是社区服务
我们要对付几个恶煞
怎么？你们不行吗？
他们不是你，明蒂
汤米卖干燥水果
暗夜骚货教芭蕾舞
暗夜骚货？她是谁？
是超级英雄还是AV女优？
都是吧
天哪，你上过她？
我要吐了
你就像女忍者一样
难道不能趁马库斯睡觉偷溜出来？
你不懂的，戴夫
我答应过马库斯
那就反悔啊，你忘了你是超级英雄？
明蒂麦奎迪只是个幌子
我不懂暗夜骚货是哪门子的超级英雄
但如果你觉得我会反悔…
那表示你不够了解我
加入舞蹈校队并不妨碍你追求自我
超杀女根本不屑
女高中生的玩意
你才不是超想约会的那种女生
去死吧
干嘛？被我说中了
壮壮小帅哥
-叫我吗？  -对啊
想约我出去吗？
想啊…
我叫…赛门
好，赛门
约好喽
明蒂，很抱歉
有问题吗，明蒂？
没事
很好，我不喜欢看到问题
戴夫，你晚上都偷溜出去？
奈波太太看到你凌晨两点出门
奈波小姐疯了，爸
她教小狗西班牙文耶
你有嗑药吗？
真的这样想？
我一定要问
你是我最好的哥们，你也长大了
答应我别做傻事？
好，我答应你
这样就够了，哥们
你很聪明，不会做傻事的
正义永存！
你能这样纾解压力不错
陶德又传讯息了，死阿宅
星条旗上校到底有多可怕啊？
真不敢相信他以前是混黑道的
黑道哪有可能变成超级英雄？
他是重获新生的基督徒
-少来了  -是真的
祈祷他今晚能全身而退
我们很快就会知道了
其他人呢？
重力博士感冒了
汤米弄到音乐剧的票…
没关系
我们5个就够了
这个人靠什么维生？胁迫卖淫？
不只女人也有小孩的，都偷渡过来的
白痴警察坐视不管
你怎么知道今晚他在？
因为星期四是扑克之夜
五个人渣准时出现
有习性的人并不难找
计划是什么？偷偷进去？
我想敲个门，这样比较有礼貌
什么?
大家保持冷静
对我来说这算小事一桩
耶和华的见证人！
对不起，我刚没听清楚
你是说对付5个黑道吗？
外加一个保镖，总共6个
又四分之三
啥咪代志？
晚安，少年仔，我们想找大金聊聊
如果他方便的话
给我滚，不然就折断你的头，死老头
打扰了
有麻烦了
搞不懂为何大家都爱耍狠
喔!
搞定一个了
神呀
单挑王，我怎么说的？别乱说妄语
我错了，上校
艾森豪，准备好
虫人，跟在我后面
其他人散开，别让人溜了
哦
试着找乐子…不然…
有什么意义呢？
这么热闹，有人想跳舞吗？
往哪跑？
-做的好  -小心后面！
注意了
哇!
别动
暗夜骚货！你后面！
留情
小心！
好，我来铐他右手
满口食物不要说话
没礼貌
你算哪根葱？
我们是正义的使者
不，你们死定了
艾森豪！鸡鸡！
够劲!
嗷!
女孩呢？
放过我吧，我有心脏病
是喔？
不要…
要我帮你吗？
哇咧，哇咧!
我招了，女孩都在公寓楼上
我弟负责收钱，他还在念大学
-屌爆侠、暗夜骚货  -包在我身上
拉夫达米柯会毙了你！
痛！
是啊，德国狼犬就爱广东咸蛋
钱都给你，桌上有五万块
拜托谁来阻止它！拜托！
你以为可以收买我们？真的这么想？
我们不是来抢钱的
我们是来打广告的…告诉其他死杂碎
-这里勒令停业  -过来…
外面有受暴妇女庇护所专车
你们会到一个安全的地方
-上车吧  -我们走不了
我们没有钱
单挑王，桌上有多少钱？
大概有五万块
够多了吧
谢谢
大伙干得好
好极了，好极了
没想到你会拿枪指着他
真的会射他吗？
说一个小秘密
空的，别告诉那些坏蛋
我就直说了，上校，你超有种的
肯定比大金多
‘那狗在咬我蛋蛋’
可恶！
-哈维尔  -怎么了？
有个蠢蛋贴了制服店的消息
屌爆侠那群人把那里掀了
搞什么？我的人呢？
大家都…
小姐，你们可以离开一下吗？
不，她们是我的助手，不用担心
她们不是你的助手
她们是妓女兼证人
-好吧  -抱歉，无意冒犯
大家都怕你叔叔拉夫所以没人做大
但他还在坐牢
没差，现在整个家族都归他管
他希望大家维持低调
但算你好运
大汤尼不懂得避风头，所以他加入了
-没印象，他很大只吗？  -小矮子
五尺四寸而已，但狠到不行
他以杀人为快乐之本
-矮冬瓜却很能杀  -没错
叫他‘致命肿瘤’吧
下一个？
他混过中国黑道
简单‘成吉痴汉’下一个
你一定要改掉种族刻板印象
那是中国伟人耶，继续
我们找到卡特莲娜丹布罗斯基
等等，母的？
对
你真的找个母的？
她做过苏联秘密警察
关在劳改营时，生吞活剥了狱友
好吧‘臭俄后’
臭俄后和臭B王在同一队？
行不通的
我不是在建议你，王八蛋
快去准备服装，顺便把人叫下来！
唉…
哈维尔，谢谢
我不能没有你
你就像我唯一的亲人
安啦，老弟，我会永远罩着你
我是反派蝙蝠侠，你就是老管家了
你说我是你的老管家？
对啊，这不算是称赞吗？
抱歉，我的错
夜晚通常没什么动静
我和暗夜骚货倒是会做些运动
超级英雄最常做的就是巡逻
但大家还是挤破头想加入
这次招募新血
再不邀请陶德，好像不够朋友
别偷看，你们会坏事
你…们…看…
穿这样怎么干架？
裤子紧到青蛙眼都出来了
什么青蛙眼？
-宅男版的激凸  -什么?
我对这些名字不予置评
‘打爆王’、‘屌爆人’
-屌爆博士？  -对
老实说，有点…延伸的感觉
我来翻译一下
你不能直接抄袭戴夫的假名，吹棒人
了…
呃…
等一下，我想到了
有了
‘爆屌侠’
在开玩笑吗？
马堤你这王八蛋
我知道你为什么不回我简讯
我不是笨蛋
你确定？舔菊人侠
-去你妈的  -陶德…
不，干你娘
我会找到自己的队友
陶德别走
陶德说的对，我们是王八蛋
但其实
我只想找明蒂进来…
…可是她忙着不当超级英雄
明蒂下来，他到了
第一次的约会，感觉如何？
我想起大老霸第一次派我去毒窟
身上只有一把小刀
我开始紧张了
做你自己就好，让我来担心
别担心，我不用动手就可以杀了他
良心建议，别拿这个当开场白
谢谢你愿意跟我约会
老实说…
我想不到其他方法阻止你夺命连环扣
-谢谢  -不客气
我们要去哪里？
参加派对
派对办在荒郊野外？
酒桶派对不都这样吗？
我们大概是第一个到
这哪是办派对的地方，傻瓜
弃尸地点倒是真的
你有问题吗？
对不起
我会正常一点
你看起来人很好
现在呢？
来亲热吧？
别傻了
赛门，躲到车里面
立刻！
你来了
布鲁克？
这…是要帮你庆祝
庆祝？
你是一个大衰鬼
而我们排挤衰鬼
可怜的明蒂，怎么样啊？
帅哥觉得你很特别
邀请你参加人生第一场派对
你会第一次喝啤酒
第一次接吻？
醒一醒吧，你普通到不行
杠上我，吃不完兜着走
约会被甩了
派对在我家！
真可怜
赛门，载我们去
戴夫？
吓死我了！明蒂？
天呀，你怎么了？
我只是…想见我的罗宾
你没事吧？
别哭
我不晓得该怎么办
那些女生，她们…
她们真邪恶
这就是高中，很快就过了
你应该回到现实世界，把世界变得更好
戴夫，我做不到
我了，你答应过爸爸
但爸爸不在了
这是你的人生，你自己要过
我明天要怎么面对她们？
超丢脸的
怎魔会？
你聪明、漂亮、幽默
你是最坚强的人，没有做不到的事
而且你是超杀女
戴着面具也没差
反正那就是你
我该怎么做？割断她们的舌头？
不！当然不行
吓到你了
运用你的优势打败她们
做你自己就好
如果想让人缘变好
就要考虑两件事，性与录影带
萝伊，不用听那些恐龙妹吹牛
我可以这么辣，你也可以
这是失踪的毒枭给的见面礼
学我们穿衣服
不一定有我们的气质
我穿什么衣服并不重要
我是超级英雄，那就是我
随便你，神鲍大侠
继续演吧
是吗？
你这个做作女
骨子里是恶毒的死八婆
鸡巴程度和社会败类有得拼
你要听实话吗，明蒂？
在现实世界我赢定了
我会考上好大学，嫁个好老公
生个可爱北鼻
到巴黎度假，还有保姆代劳
我的人生棒透了，你的人生烂毙了
还有，不管你穿得多骚
男生都不想亲你那一张臭嘴
我要是你早就割腕自杀了
再多看你一秒
我就会倒胃口
-说的好  -活该
那是什么？智障手机？
词穷了要搬救兵？
不瞒你说
这是我爸从国防部弄来的
本来用在场控，但效果太猛了
它会发射电波，让人呕吐腹泻
我爸叫它‘呕吐棒’
要不是你爸遇到诈骗集团
就是你在做梦，亲爱的
因为我们感觉超良好
就快了
哇…哩…咧…
别弄我，求求你，你赢了
我不想赢，我只是想把世界变好
爸？
在家吗？爸？
我轮夜班赚学费，你却在搞这个？
原来你都在变装打架？
这棍子竟然还有血迹
你来我房间干什么？
我来找毒品
我担心你
你可以放心了
我更担心了
嗑药还好一些
这太…疯狂了
我还好吧
跟你的同伙比起来？
不，他们都是超级英雄
那是漫画
真实世界是要负责任的
你何时才会长大？
我永远不要变成你这样
我戴面具不是因为感到羞耻
不像你
什么意思？
休假只会练腹肌
干吗这样？只为了学别人？
浑浑噩噩又过了几年？
爸，你的人生没有意义
你死了有谁会知道？
你要去哪里？
离家出走，长大会做的事
他有说为什么想见我吗？
你叔叔拉夫打来，我也没多问
只要他
克里斯，别慌，不会有事的
过得怎样？
很好，拉夫叔叔
听我说，你爸过世以后
情况变得一团糟
我一直想让整个家族回归正轨
他们在录音
我知道，随他们
典狱长是我的人，专心听我说
玩玩是没关系
但干嘛雇用一票职业杀手
哈维尔早该告诉你的
我心意已决
我要屌爆侠为他的行为付出代价
你还是忘了吧
你最好别淌浑水
你不像我或你爸，你…
比较特别
我不会听你的
我知道我是谁了
喔，是吗？
你是谁？
臭B王
你自以为是狠角色，是吗？
我来告诉你什么是真正的坏胚子
喂？
哈维尔没事吧？
怎么了？
你干嘛打别人的手机？
手机又掉到马桶了？
没事吧？
谢谢你教我这些，我很需要
未来会很有用
别干蠢事，克里斯
暂时避个风头，念大学做什么都好
何必呢？该学的你都教了
你看
快狠准，小鬼们想出超杀的队徽
怎么啦？听到什么吗？
我们去看看，来！
有人吗？
什么都没有
冷静了再来找我，你疯疯的
真好奇你在烦什么
我知道，因为今晚是你的死期
女士优先
你不会射我的
你是超级英雄
乐于助人，不会伤人
只有超级坏蛋才会做
我们军团的名字是…
万毒巨掰
嗨
跟你的头一样空
耶!
一定很痛吧
我调查过你，星条旗上校
你就是塞尔贝托里尼吧？
‘重生’以前还帮我爸做过事情
我以前都跟鳖三一起混
你有想过会这么死吗？
穿得像智障一样
你又是谁？
臭B王！
我来干掉屌爆侠，不只是毙了他
还要毁了他所爱的一切
掀了这个鬼地方
‘米兰达史瓦德洛’？
她是谁？队里的野女人？
暗夜骚货…贴着屌爆侠有够紧
看来男人有新的泄欲工具了
要我杀了这只狗吗？
这只狗？你嘛帮帮忙，我没那么邪恶
割下他的头
不饿吗？我饿死了，快点
可以叫披萨吗？
有披萨吃喽
别急，先杀了你再说
正义…
永存
布鲁克林区一位居民昨晚遭到斩首
根据推特资料，有一个人…
自称是全世界第一个超级坏蛋
我说过别看电视，忘记你被禁足了？
我是答应过你…
但我不可能一直装成别人
我看到邪恶就无法坐视不管
你对那些女人太残忍了
-你差点害死她们  -我是可以
最后只是让她们回家狂泻
真可惜
一心只想着报复，有害身心健康
这种事情再不交给我们警察处理
我就真的救不了你
你会像你爸一样
无法过正常生活
他们砍了那个人的头
谁来阻止他们？
屌爆侠？还是你？
给我回房间做功课
马上！
我们合签一张慰问卡送给上校姐姐
每人出五块合买一束花好不好？
你有看到臭B王的推特页吗？
干嘛提到他？
我不知道，但他胆子超大
一直吹嘘是他杀了星条旗上校
找得到他吗？
我试过了，他把IP隐藏起来了
我们来开战吧
很多人想声援我们
这可不是西城故事
我们不是来混黑道的…
我们是来帮助别人的…
雪伦说的对，这个应该交给警察处理
以后最好团体行动
臭B王说，上校的死只是开始
有人见到暗夜骚货吗？
你确定她是一挂的？
这个笨蛋在她的粉丝专页
说自己和屌爆侠正在交往
我很确定就是她
早安，暗夜骚货！
嘿
她觉得楼上比较适合开趴
开趴罗
她关了门
别怕，亲爱的，我不会杀你
我要你传话给你的男朋友
来嘛
放开我！
宝贝，你用过超级英雄的鸡巴
这次让你试试看超级坏蛋的屌
可恶
怎么了？
你在干嘛？
快啊！
算了，我没兴致
大概是恶屌不举吧
把她…打成猪头！
条子来了
留给臭俄后
她时薪是我们的十倍
一周五万，生活费另计
小心！
哇咧!
快倒车！
别动！
五万，值回票价
他们干嘛倒车？
为什么有除草机？
哇咧!
增派警力，八个挂了
是十个啦
快走！
帮我打广告，邪恶军团蓄势待发
欢迎精神失常、坐过牢的共襄盛举
大家一定都会抢着来
他们就这样消失了？
换上便服
就没人认得出来
大家听我说！
我们有所有变装怪客的IP位址
全国执法机关
将会一举逮捕他们
怎魔会有屌爆侠？
他们是做社区服务
我不管，变装的全部给我抓起来
今晚就要做个了结
大家都说警方那天晚上执法过当
但平心而论
警方根本不在乎什么是正港的英雄
只要我们捡垃圾
或扶老妇人过马路
但这次出了大代志
我们顿时成了社会罪恶的代名词
别动！
爸警告过我真实世界是要负责任的
警察来的时候他肯定觉得自己料事如神
这小子，到底干了什么事？
警察，开门
嘿
嗨
是我，屌爆侠
哇
本人还真可爱
我很抱歉你发生这种事
不甘你的事
是我自找的
我们要找到这些王八蛋，为你报仇
有意义吗？
英雄或约会
对我们来说是一样的虚假
我们甚至不知道彼此的姓名
是该回归现实的时候了
我以为我们都想让世界变得更好
怎么反而变得更糟？
或许暗夜骚货说的对…
我爸也说中了
我是指，情势失控了
我是该回家
跟爸爸道歉了吧
爸？
那是我爸
你爸是屌爆侠？
他刚刚承认了
你不懂，他只是为了保护我
爸！
-明蒂？  -戴夫？
我爸被捕了
警方以为他是屌爆侠
你可以跟马库斯说一声吗？
-我被禁足了  -所以呢？
我管不了
-等一下  -我无能为力
明蒂，你有在听吗？
我要挂了
抱歉，戴夫
明蒂，别挂
你到底在想什么？
我才要问你
你怎么可以骗他们？
我不会让你坐牢的
你应该让我自行承担后果
我以为你希望我长大
你当了爸妈就会懂的
我要跟他们说实话
不，事情只会愈来愈糟
律师说
明天就可以回家
罪名都不成立
外面有很多人想杀屌爆侠
这里有警察看着
关在这里才是最安全的
我不知道你怎么惹到这些麻烦，但…
你要答应我别再穿那套衣服
听到了吗？
我答应你
这个大本营大家都说赞！
听起来有点老派
黑白讲
你的鲨鱼快挂了
大概是水的问题
搞什么，伊亚？
你放心，鲨鱼喜欢躺在水槽底部
这是它们融入环境的方式
别呼咙我
你说两天就会完工
结果连厕所都没有
你放心
那几袋垃圾是啥？
做炸弹用的
不摧毁整座城市就不算超级坏蛋
没用的，化学肥料才行
我什么事情都要自己来吗？
还不去弄!
放轻松，一切会照计划进行
但可惜没有，懂吗？
那个替死鬼不是屌爆侠
我看过他本人，就跟我同年纪
那个人都可以当他爸了
没错
不好意思，你哪位？
我是来加入你的军团的
欢迎，肛温，感谢你为邪恶而战
这里是核心成员VIP专区
我只是觉得你很好笑
因为他就是屌爆侠的爸爸
谁？
莱佐斯基先生，屌爆侠他爸
少来了！
真的，别告诉其他人
我不会
但是你刚取得了VIP永久会员身分
找位置坐
给他一杯星冰乐…
再叫这个猪头去工作
知道了
过来
有事吗？
臭B王要我们一起合照
安啦，我爸是一流的律师
不然我在监狱
肯定会被肛肛好
怪了，克里斯达米柯竟然传照片给我
赤雾侠？他怎么样了？
到底是什么？
戴夫，怎么了？
我后来几天浑浑噩噩
无论我跟警方怎么描述克里斯…
他们就是找不到人
警察也来参加我爸的葬礼
不是出于尊重
而是想避免恐怖事件
我爸是个好人
他总是努力让我过好日子
我竟然跟他说，他死了没人会知道
我爱你，哥们
我也爱你，爸
你们来了
我们想帮你追查克里斯这个人渣
但我们还在假释期
没关系
我并不想复仇
我最后答应爸爸不再变装
我说到做到
这是你起的头
现在由我结束
很抱歉，你会恨我见死不救吗？
不，一点也不
你是对的，你退出了
如果我也退出，我爸就不会死
我只怪我自己
大开杀戒！
趴下！
明蒂！
散开！
压低身体！
过来！
哇-哩-咧!
去抓他！
把货车开过来！
快点！
明蒂？
明蒂！
把这个穿上
门都没有
你伤不了我的
你确定？
哇!咧!
开战吧，死杂碎
车顶有个女孩！
她还在
-我甩掉她了  -去确认
出去搞定！
把头移开
停车，阴毛脸
我们知道克里斯就是臭B王
他躲在哪里？
舔我的老二
不说就让你舔自己的
杀了我吧，小贱人
你没有办法逼我说的
住手，时机不对，这是我爸的葬礼
戴夫，你爸很爱你
就像我爸很爱我，我知道很痛苦
但或许这是成为超级英雄的意义
承受痛苦，化悲愤为力量
正义的力量
还记得你说过的话吗？
这是你的人生，你自己要过
帮我找钳子，我要让他吸自己的老二
说真的？
-喂？  -马库斯？
怎么了？你没事吧？
我很好
我们知道臭B王躲在哪里
他组了邪恶军团，正在制作炸弹
他想炸了这个城市
你答应过我
我知道你把我当成小女孩
但我不是，从来都不是
你说得对
大老霸确实剥夺我的童年
但我不觉得是坏事
他教我的本领
我说什么也无法忘记
我不用浪费四年
寻找自我
因为我早就知道
我是超杀女
我贴了地址，他们会来吗？
克里斯有一票人耶
他们一辈子就等着这个机会，会来的
你没事吧？
什么？没事，我很好
这个
拿着
用这个不符合我的行事风格
戴夫，这不是漫画
今晚会有人死的
我爸都会做好万全准备
你呢？
嗯
准备好了
他们应该到了吧！
绝对死了
网路上说要用淡水养鲨鱼
它只是饿了，喂它东西吃
干嘛看着我？
我们要马上开始
没错，我为你们这群人准备了一场秀
臭B王，臭B王…
够了，派对咖！
我们要一起杀了屌爆侠
第一个超级英雄
我们要把他碎尸万段
喂饱这只鎚头鲨
再把影片上传，说到做到！
这是开玩笑吧？
臭B王说到做到
不只这样，我会发给每个人…
派对良伴甲烷炸弹！
我们要让世界大乱!
这才叫邪恶
我们才是社会菁英…
今晚要闹翻这座城市，否则我就不叫…
克里斯达米柯!
那不是我的名字！
对，那不是，你的本名是小孬孬
噢，老天爷真帮我
你真的那么脑残？
两个人也想找我们单挑
真的那么想死？
不…
所以我们还撂人来
怎么了，克里斯？闪尿了？
对，等你帮我舔干净
你要为我爸的死付出代价
你爸？你用火箭筒杀了我爸
噢!
想死了吗，小屁孩？
如果继续看你的屎脸，我可能很想死
克里斯！
压住他，我想看他多有能耐
你们真是够了！
干得好，亲爱的
就这样？
不，还有我的零重力装置
瞎掰
是真的
没事吧？
没事，谢谢，爆屌侠
干得好
天啊,你还真孬
没本是装什么英雄
我们想要主持正义
才怪，一般人只想中乐透
只想睡正妹
凭那根针也想杀我？
你会错意了
这是肾上腺素，贱货
干嘛？偷吃步？
你欠上校的
啊!
这是你欠暗夜骚货的
这是你欠我爸的
你想干什么？
救你这个靠爸族!
不！
我才不要，我宁愿死！
你还当真？这不是漫画，这是人生！
你死了就一了百了，没有续集
你造的孽，你起的头！
让我来终结这一切
我会受后世传颂，就像邪恶耶稣
等一下！
我还活着
戴夫，让你失望了
这感觉难以言喻
克里斯达米柯，死了
他自称的邪恶军团，败了
但世界真的有变好吗？
还是说仅仅收拾了…
这套服装所制造的问题
警察快来了
他们会搞定那些坏蛋
大家最好趁机溜走
我们办到了
我靠
别说脏话
你说的对，扮英雄就要有英雄的样子
他会以你为荣，戴夫
他会以大家为荣
这是最后一次了吧？
结束了
最后一次呐喊，来吧
你呢，超杀女？要来吗？
没差
正义永存！
谢谢你载我回家
学校见
我要离开纽约，戴夫
我不能回家，我不想马库斯难做人
为什么？他不会逮捕你的
你救了整座城市
我还拿警用手枪杀了六个人
我用的是私行
你不能走，大家需要你
-他们有你就够了  -明蒂…
我比不上你
当英雄不一定要很猛，戴夫
只要有勇气就够了
这是？
我的初吻
好好做人
不然就把你屁股从嘴里扯出来
明蒂离开以后
我总算看清方向
这个世界总有人…
想当超级英雄
但总有终结的一刻
超级英雄无法存在于真实世界
原因只有一个
真实世界只需要正港的英雄
不是穿潜水服的变装癖
而是真正屌爆的英雄们
哈罗？
拜托！别走
别走！
那有人吗？
哈罗？
请给我一些帮助！
鲨鱼咬掉了我的鸡鸡，这他妈的叫我怎么喝水？
字
字幕
字幕制
字幕制作
字幕制作 ★
字幕制作 ★ 至
字幕制作 ★ 至宏
字幕制作 ★ 至宏上
字幕制作 ★ 至宏上人